RG 074:071, Robert Hilands McKeon Genealogical Papers
Connecticut State Library
Robert Hilands McKeon genealogical papers
circa 1990-1997
circa 1795-1954
Connecticut State Library
McKeon, Robert Hilands
1 cubic foot
Primarily copies of military, pension, and family records. Family names include Goodsell, Highland, Hiland, Hilands, Hoyland, Hoylands, Lowry, McKinney, Mitcheltree, Reznor, and Williams.
RG074_071
2012-030
Scope and Content
Primarily copies of military, pension, and family records. Family names include Goodsell, Highland, Hiland, Hilands, Hoyland, Hoylands, Lowry, McKinney, Mitcheltree, Reznor, and Williams.
The Goodsell genealogy traces the Goodsell family from immigrant Thomas Goodsell (1646-1713) of New Haven, Connecticut. This volume includes information on the Averill, Blossom, Cogswell, Ferriss, Fitz Randolph, Ford, Gaylord, Goodsell, Jackson, Loweree, Noble, Penfield, Ross, Smith, and Stanley families. Three folders of miscellaneous materials including correspondence, family notes and charts, newspaper clippings, and photographs were removed from between the pages of the volume.
Index Terms
Family Names:
Goodsell family; Highland family; Hiland family; Hilands family; Hoyland family; Hoylands family; Lowry family; McKinney family; Mitcheltree family; Reznor family; Williams family
Places:
Connecticut -- Genealogy; Ohio -- Genealogy; Pennsylvania -- Genealogy
Document Types:
Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence; Genealogies; Military records; Photographs; Scrapbooks
Restrictions on Access
These papers are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Papers, circa 1900-1997
  - Highland, Daniel B. (Box 1)
    Died 1863
    Civil War military and family records, 80th Ohio Volunteer Regiment, Company A
  - John Highland - War of 1812 (Box 1)
    Born 1795, Died 1873
    Pension records, Pennsylvania
  - John Hiland - Ohio - Militia Barry Michigan - War of 1812 (Box 1)
    Born circa 1797
  - Abraham T. Hilands (Box 1)
    Born 1826, Died 1887
    Civil War military and family records, 49th Pennsylvania Volunteer Infantry Regiment, Company F & staff
  - Hilands, Daniel (Box 1)
    Born circa 1839, Died 1864
    6th Pennsylvania Volunteer Heavy Artillery Regiment, Company I
  - Highlands, John - War of 1812 - PA (Box 1)
  - Highlands, Reuben Valentine - Civil War records (Box 1)
    Born 1822, Died 1904
    Military and family records. 105th Ohio Volunteer Infantry Regiment, Company C.
  - Hoyland, John Walter - Civil War records (Box 1)
    Born 1824, Died 1914
    31st Wisconsin Volunteer Infantry Regiment, Company B
  - Hoyland, William B. - Spanish American War (Box 1)
    Born 1877, Died 1961
    Pension records, 1st Wisconsin Volunteer Infantry Regiment, Company H
  - Hoylands, Alexander - Civil War records (Box 1)
    Born 1837, Died 1921
    Pension and family records. 90th Ohio Volunteer Infantry Regiment, Company B.
  - Hoylands, Benjamin Louis - Civil War records (Box 1)
    Born 1827, Died 1911
    Pension and family records. 38th Wisconsin Volunteer Infantry Regiment, Company D.
  - Hoylands, David P. - Civil War records (Box 2)
    Born 1837, Died 1912
    Military and family records. 2nd Ohio Volunteer Infantry Regiment, Company E.
  - Hoylands, Robert W. - 53 Ohio Infantry - Killed in action (Box 2)
    Born 1844, Died 1864
    Military and family records. 53rd Ohio Volunteer Infantry Regiment, Company E.
  - Ward Alexander Lowry (Box 2)
    Born 1884, Died 1954
    World War I pension and family records.
  - McKinney, Edward M. (Box 2)
    Born 1859, Died 1922
    Spanish-American War pension, probate & family records, United States 6th Cavalry and 16th Pennsylvania VOlunteer Infantry Regiment, Company D.
  - Reznor, George (Box 2)
    Died 1911
    Civil War pension records, 39th Pennsylvania Volunteer Infantry Regiment, Company G.
  - Williams, Jesse R. (Box 2)
    Born 1830, Died 1914
    Civil War, Pennsylvania pension and Soldier Home records.
  - Independent Hornets (Box 2)
    Mercer County, Pennsylvania, militia listing of the "Independent Hornets" circa 1846.
  - War of 1812, Sons of (Box 2)
  - "The Record of My Ancestry. The Goodsell Family Book of Origins, Private and Personal, With Hisotrical Notes, Coats of Arms, and Photographs. Traced by Buel Goodsell and Bertha Goodsell", 1 volume + 3 folders of items removed from between pages of volume (Box 2)
  - Mitchell Family family record (Box 2)
    Color photocopies of three family record sheets of the John Irvin Mitcheltree (1824-1875) and Fanny Jane (DeForest) Mitcheltree (1826-1874) Family.